export const QuestionData = [
  {
    question: "What is the population of Indore?",
    options: ["1 million", "2 million", "3 million", "4 million"],
    answer: "3 million",
  },
  {
    question: "Which river flows through Indore?",
    options: ["Ganges", "Narmada", "Yamuna", "Krishna"],
    answer: "Narmada",
  },
  {
    question: "Which is the largest commercial center in Indore?",
    options: [
      "Rajwada",
      "Sarafa Bazaar",
      "Treasure Island Mall",
      "Chappan Dukan",
    ],
    answer: "Treasure Island Mall",
  },
  {
    question: "Which famous educational institute is located in Indore?",
    options: ["IIT Indore", "IIM Indore", "BITS Pilani", "NIT Indore"],
    answer: "IIM Indore",
  },
  {
    question: "Which is the official language of Indore?",
    options: ["Hindi", "English", "Marathi", "Malwi"],
    answer: "Hindi",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the popular street food of Indore?",
    options: ["Poha", "Samosa", "Kachori", "Daal Bafla"],
    answer: "Poha",
  },
  {
    question: "Which is the largest stadium in Indore?",
    options: [
      "Nehru Stadium",
      "Holkar Stadium",
      "Emerald Heights International School Ground",
      "Maharani Usharaje Trust Cricket Ground",
    ],
    answer: "Holkar Stadium",
  },
  {
    question: "Which historical monument is located in Indore?",
    options: ["Taj Mahal", "Red Fort", "Kanch Mahal", "Rajwada"],
    answer: "Rajwada",
  },
  {
    question: "Which festival is celebrated with great enthusiasm in Indore?",
    options: ["Diwali", "Holi", "Ganesh Chaturthi", "Navratri"],
    answer: "Ganesh Chaturthi",
  },
  {
    question: "Which is the largest park in Indore?",
    options: [
      "Nehru Park",
      "Kamla Nehru Park",
      "Rajwada Garden",
      "Mhow Cantt Garden",
    ],
    answer: "Kamla Nehru Park",
  },
];
